[
  {
    "id": "428",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using multiple learning algorithms and models collectively to improve the model accuracy",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "429",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Supervised open-source implementation of the gradient boosted trees algorithm that attempts to accurately predict a target variable by combining the estimates of a set of simpler, weaker models",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "430",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A virtual swiss army knife for all sorts of regression, classification, and ranking problems, with 2 required and 35 optional hyperparameters to tune",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "431",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Accepts CSV and libsvm for training and inference",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "432",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Uses tabular data with rows representing observations, one column representing the target variable or label, and the remaining columns representing features",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "433",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Only trains on CPU and memory-bound as opposed to compute bound",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "434",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "AWS recommends you give it lots of memory",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "435",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Use and instance with enough memory to hold the entire training data for optimal performance",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "436",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using the SageMaker Spark SDK, you can call ______ directly from within the Spark environment",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "437",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Use case: Ranking - On an e-commerce website, you can leverage data about search results, clicks, and successful purchases, and then use ______ to train a model that can return relevance scores for searched products",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "438",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Use case: Fraud detection - When ______ is given a dataset of past transactions and whether or not they were fraudulent, it can learn a function that maps input transaction data to the probability that transaction was fraudulent",
      "answers": [
        "Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA)",
        "Neural Topic Model",
        "Sequence to sequence",
        "Blazing text",
        "Object2Vec",
        "DeepAR",
        "Reinforcement Learning",
        "XGBoost"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["XGBoost"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "439",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are being asked to develop a model to predict the likelihood that a student will pass a certification exam based on hours of study. Of the options given, what would be the best approach to this problem?",
      "answers": [
        "Build a clustering mode with K-Means to group students who pass in a cluster.",
        "Build a model using NLP to classify students into passing and failing groups.",
        "Build a simulation-based model which will analyze past student performance at varying levels of study.",
        "Build a model using LDA based on the text of the questions on the exam and predict student outcome.",
        "Build a Logistic Regression model using the hours of study as as a feature."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Build a Logistic Regression model using the hours of study as as a feature."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "440",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which of the following are good candidate problems for using XGBoost? (Choose 3)",
      "answers": [
        "Map a text string to an n-gram vector.",
        "Create a policy that will guide an autonomous robot through an unknown maze.",
        "Deciding whether a transaction is fraudulent or not based on various details about the transaction.",
        "Providing a ranking of search results on an e-commerce site customized to a customer's past purchases.",
        "Evaluate handwritten numbers on a warranty card to detect what number they represent."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deciding whether a transaction is fraudulent or not based on various details about the transaction.",
        "Providing a ranking of search results on an e-commerce site customized to a customer's past purchases.",
        "Evaluate handwritten numbers on a warranty card to detect what number they represent."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "441",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which best describes SGD in common terms?",
      "answers": [
        "Calculate the linear distance between arrows shot into a target to determine accuracy.",
        "Attempt to find the most efficient path to deliver packages to multiple destinations.",
        "Seek to find the lowest point in elevation on a landscape.",
        "Ensure that our sample size in a traffic study has at least 30 drivers."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Seek to find the lowest point in elevation on a landscape."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "442",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You have been asked to help develop a vision system for a manufacturing line that will reorient parts to a specific position using a robotic arm. What algorithm might you choose for the vision part of this problem?",
      "answers": [
        "Image Analysis",
        "AWS Comprehend",
        "Seq2Seq",
        "Object2Vec",
        "Semantic Segmentation",
        "Object Detection"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Semantic Segmentation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "443",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When analyzing a set of one-hot encoded data you realize that, while there is a massive amount of data, most of the values are absent. This is expected given the type of data, but what built-in SageMaker algorithm might you choose to work with this data?",
      "answers": [
        "Object2Vec",
        "K-Nearest Neighbor",
        "Semantic Segmentation",
        "Linear Learner",
        "Factorization Machines"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Factorization Machines"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "444",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are on a personal quest to design the best chess playing model in the world. What might be a good strategy for this objective?",
      "answers": [
        "Use a Factorization Machine approach to analyze the winning series of moves across thousands of chess matches to find the best series of moves.",
        "Use an unsupervised learning strategy to analyze similarities across thousands of the best chess matches.",
        "Use Mechanical Turk to crowdsource the best chess moves in a variety of scenarios then use those for a supervised learning session.",
        "Use a supervised learning strategy that is trained by feeding in the chess moves of thousands of famous chess experts.",
        "Use a reinforcement learning strategy to let the model learn itself."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a reinforcement learning strategy to let the model learn itself."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "445",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of unsupervised learning? (Choose 2)",
      "answers": [
        "Using Seq2Seq to extract a text string from a segment of a recorded speech.",
        "Using K-Means to cluster customers into demographic segments.",
        "Using NTM to extract topics from a set of scientific journal articles.",
        "Using XGBoost to predict the selling price of a house in a particular market.",
        "Using a Factorization Machine to provide book recommendations."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Using K-Means to cluster customers into demographic segments.",
        "Using NTM to extract topics from a set of scientific journal articles."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "446",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which of these examples would be considered as introducing bias into a problem space? (Choose 2)",
      "answers": [
        "Deciding to use a supervised learning method to estimate missing values in a dataset.",
        "Omitting records before a certain date in a forecasting problem.",
        "Failing to randomize a dataset even though you were told it was already random.",
        "Filtering out outliers in a dataset which are greater than 4 standard deviations outside the mean.",
        "Removing records from a set of customer reviews that were not fully complete."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Failing to randomize a dataset even though you were told it was already random.",
        "Removing records from a set of customer reviews that were not fully complete."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "447",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the following might be used to focus a model on most relevant features?",
      "answers": [
        "NLM",
        "AQS",
        "K-NN",
        "LDA",
        "XGB",
        "PCA"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["PCA"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "448",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In what scenario is the DeepAR algorithm best suited?",
      "answers": [
        "Decide whether to extend a credit card offer to a potential customer.",
        "Predict whether a football team will score a certain number of points in a match.",
        "Predict future sales of a new product based on historic sales of similar products.",
        "Provide the certainty that a given picture includes a human face.",
        "Determine the correlation between a person's diet and energy levels."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Predict future sales of a new product based on historic sales of similar products."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "449",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You are consulting for a shipping company who wants to implement a very specific algorithm for shipping container optimization. The algorithm is not part of the currently available SageMaker built-in algorithms. What are your options? (Choose 2)",
      "answers": [
        "Build the algorithm in a docker container and use that custom algorithm for training and inference in SageMaker.",
        "Search the AWS Marketplace for the algorithm. If it exists, deploy it using SageMaker for inferences.",
        "Wait until the algorithm is available in SageMaker before further work.",
        "Post an incendiary message to Twitter hoping to shame AWS into adopting the specialized algorithm.",
        "Use a series of existing algorithms to simulate the actions of the unavailable algorithm."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Build the algorithm in a docker container and use that custom algorithm for training and inference in SageMaker.",
        "Search the AWS Marketplace for the algorithm. If it exists, deploy it using SageMaker for inferences."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "450",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "While using K-Means, what does it mean if we pass in k=4 as a hyperparameter?",
      "answers": [
        "We want the algorithm to return the top 4 results.",
        "We want the algorithm to group into clusters of no more than 4 samples each.",
        "We want the algorithm to use 4 as the cutoff value for classification purposes.",
        "We want the algorithm to classify into 4 groups.",
        "We want the algorithm to group into 4 clusters."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["We want the algorithm to group into 4 clusters."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "451",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To remove inconsistency in a process, you have created a very specific step-by-step process for patching servers. How would this best be described?",
      "answers": [
        "The procedure is a work-around until a supervised learning process can be implemented which will remove the human from the process.",
        "The procedure is an algorithm as it will allow the person performing the upgrades to choose the best path.",
        "The procedure is an algorithm as it will yield a consistent output.",
        "The procedure is a heuristic as it will yield a consistent output.",
        "The procedure is a heuristic as it permits the person performing the upgrades from making unintended mistakes."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["The procedure is an algorithm as it will yield a consistent output."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "452",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Modeling",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You are consulting with a retailer that wants to evaluate the sentiment of social media posts to determine if they are positive or negative. Which approach would be the most direct to this problem?",
      "answers": [
        "Use BlazingText in Word2Vec mode for skip-gram.",
        "Use Object2Vec in sentiment detection mode.",
        "Use Amazon Macie.",
        "Use BlazingText in Text Classification mode.",
        "Use Amazon Comprehend."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Comprehend."]
    }
  }
]